export default data = [
  {
      question: "Due to a budget cut, our company’s annual year-end party, which is usually quite a treat, has to be held at a ______ cost.",
      options: ["hostile","barren","minimal","systematic"],
      correct_option: "minimal"
  },
  {
      question: "A plot to rob the bank was ______ to the police, and all the people involved in the plan were caught.",
      options: ["revealed","cancelled","declared","explored"],
      correct_option: "revealed"
  },
  {
      question: "One good way to ______ questions you don’t want to answer in a conversation is to change the topic.",
      options: ["whip","split","litter","dodge"],
      correct_option: "dodge"
  },
  {
      question: "To apply for a job, you need to have ______ such as skills, education, and experience required by the job.",
      options: ["regulations","qualifications","preventions","conventions"],
      correct_option: "qualifications"
  },
  {
      question: "For years, Lily has been ______ all incoming calls on both her mobile phone and home phone because she hates to be bothered by unknown callers.",
      options: ["glittering","purifying","mimicking","filtering"],
      correct_option: "filtering"
  },
  {
      question: "Many people felt extremely sad and angry over the ______ news of a stray dog found abused and killed in the park. ",
      options: ["flexible","sorrowful","eventual","optional"],
      correct_option: "sorrowful"
  },
  {
      question: "Chris never shows up at meetings on time. His excuse for being ______ late is that he wants to avoid small talk at the beginning of the meetings.",
      options: ["consistently"," respectfully","indifferently","enormously"],
      correct_option: "consistently"
  },
  {
      question: "Steve will quit his job next week. His ______ is completely unexpected, especially after his promotion and pay raise two months ago. ",
      options: ["approval","enforcement","resignation","signature"],
      correct_option: "resignation"
  },
  {
      question: "People with an ______ illness should avoid going to public places to keep the diseases from spreading.",
      options: ["outrageous","infectious","ultimate","explicit"],
      correct_option: "infectious"
  },
  {
      question: "10. Although electronic devices are very popular nowadays, paper ______ are still most common in major elections around the world. ",
      options: ["tokens","fragments","ballots","warranties"],
      correct_option: "ballots"
  },
]